Guide to the Ernest J. Sternglass papers, [ca. 1952-2008]
Sternglass, Ernest J. papers
- Alphabetical File List
  - Oppenheim, Bernard (University of Chicago), 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Oregon. Opposition to Nuclear Power, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Osann, Edward. Correspondence on Intervention, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Pacific News Service, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Parapsychology, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Patent (Diode Imaging), 1976-1988 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Patent. Diodes, Scan, 1977-1987 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Patent License Agreement. Scantech, Philips 1980-1984, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Patent Matters. Mammogram and Electronic Radiogram, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Patent (On Strip-Diodes), 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Patents - 1977, 1977-1982 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Patents. DADR Related. Diode Radiation, Stereo Scanning, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Patents - Diode Application Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Pauling, L., 1970-1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Peace and Conflict Seminar - 1975, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Peace Research Groups (COPRED), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Peach Bottom, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Pelvimetry and Other Techniques, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pendleton, Rob C, 1962-1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pennebaker (Esquire) Three Mile Island, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Environmental Coalition, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Vitality Statistics. Cancer, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Perry and Davis Besse Opposition (1993), 1973-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Perry and Davis Testimony - 1985 Besse Test, 1970-1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Perry Nuclear Reactor. Percent of Life Birth Weight, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Personal Health, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pesticides (DDT). Data, Distribution, 1968-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Pesticides and Radiation. Food and Water Inc., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Pesticides. Relative Effects Comapared With Radiation, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Petkau, A. Oxygen Papers and Related. Effects on Bone Marrow, etc., 1973-1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Petkau. Radiation Effects on Mambranes, 1970-1997 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Petkau. Effects Flier and Information. 1995, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Petkau Effect. Introduction EJS (1994) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Philadelphia. Health Statistics, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Philosophy, Religion, Science and Society, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Philosophy of Science and History of Science. Clippings and Articles 1972, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Philosophy of Science: Research Support Sources. National Science Foundation, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Pilgrim Leukemia Study. Massachusetts. December 7, 1990, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Pilgrim Report - June 10, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Pinellas, Florida. Plant Data, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Pinellas Plant Data, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - pisello, D. M. Infant Mortality and Sr-90, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh and Allegheny - Vitality Statistics, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Pittsburg Area Data on Radiation. Sr, Cs, Air, Water, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Pittsburgh Cancer Graphs and Data. Respiration, Heart Disease, Etc., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Pittsburgh Infant Mortality. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Plans for Articles on Nuclear Damage, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Plowshare. Clippings, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Plum Brook Reactor. Discharge Details, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Plutonium Properties, 1969-1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Pohl, R, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - pomerance, Jo. Test Ban (Total), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Pope John XXIII "Pacem in Terris" (Order in Universe), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Population and Pollution. Mathematical Analysis of Effects, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Prairie Islind. Fuel Pool, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Prematurity. Effects. US. Helen Chase, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Prematurity and Radiation, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Pressurized Water Reactor (PWR) "Zero Release System", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Progressive, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Protein Crisis. world UN, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Public Data Access (PDA) Mississippi River Study 1988. Ben Goldman. (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Public Interest Research Group (PIRG). Indiana University, 1972-1985 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Publishers (Possible for My Book on Radiation and Cosmology), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Quantum and Classical Description of Atom. Gryzhinsky, 1965-1982 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Radford, E, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Radiation Damage. DNA Repair Processes, 1971-1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Radiation Dose Calculation. Internal, Errors, Risk vs. Benefit Calculations, 1968-1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Radiation Dose Calculation. Reactor Accidents. All Isotopes., 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Radiation Dose-Rate Effect Evidence and Implications. Risk. Medical vs. Environmental. STDs, 1974-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Radiation Doses. Nuclear Medical Procedures, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Radiation Effects on Animals, 1967-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Radiation Effects. Crop Yield, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Radiation Effects. Eyes, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Radiation Effects. Organ Function, 1961-1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Radiation Effects on Plants; Diseases, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Radiation Effects. Tooth Decay, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Radiation and Evolution, Space (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Radiation Falout Effects on Weather. Ice Crystal Formation, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Radiation Health Course 1972 (RH 211) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Radiation and Mental Deterioration, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Radiation Protection. Chemicals and Actions, 1958-1965 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Radiation Protection Society (German), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Radiation Research Institute (California). Private, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Radiation Risk. Computer Terminology, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Radiation Standards. AEC New Proposal, 1960-1980 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Radiation Standards. Occupational, 1960-1980 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Radium, Cancer, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Radiation, Risk, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Rancho Seco - 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Rancho Seco 1981-1986, 1985-2000 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Rare Gases (Xe, A) Doses, 1963-1974 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Rasmussen Report Analysis, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Reactor Materials Problems, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Reproduction, Radiation Effects On, 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Respiratory Disease Mortality and Fallout. Respiratory distress, Pituitary Glands, 1963-1974 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Respiratory Distress, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Respiratory Distress in Infants, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Rimland, B. Fallout and IQ. Navy Study, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Rocky Flats, 1975-1981 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - ROMCOE (Rocky Mountains Center on Environment) Conference, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Russian Academy of Science Research (1996) On Cellular Level (Kogarto, I. N.) (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Russia. Chernobyl (Kiev Environmental Group), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Russian Life Expectancy Decline, 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Russian Translation of "Petkau Effect", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Saenger, Eugene (University of Cincinnati), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Sakharov and Other Russian, 1958-1999 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Sandler, Rivka. Bone Study, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Sandler, Rivka. Grant Application, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Sandosky. Vitality Statistics (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - SAT and Fallout. Tim Seveneres I-131 Correlation, 1968-1984 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Savannah River Project. EIS Attack 1991 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Scantech. License and Business Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Scheer, Jens and Bajer. Attempt to Force Them Out, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Scheer, J. 1985-1986 Correspondence, 1974-1991 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Scheer, Jens (1988 German Infant Mortality Data), 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Scheer, J. 1988 Muenster Paper, 1988-1993 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Scheer, Jens 1991 Correspondence, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Schenectady. Vitality Statistics, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Schubert, Jack, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Schweiker, Senator, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Science, Society and Human Values, 19880-1982 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - science and Society. Secrecy, 1969-1979 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Science, Technology and Society. Human Values Newsletter, 1974-1982 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Scott, K.G. Papers and Bibliography, 1967-1974 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Scott. Low-Level Radiation Natural Effects Studies., 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - "Secret Fallout", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Secondary Electron Emission, 1957-1978 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Secondary Electron Plasma Oscillation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Secret Fallout. Book Correspondence With Publisher, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "Secret Fallout" McGraw Hill Contract, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Segi, M. Data, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Selzer, Arter. Study, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Shapiro, M. Shippingport Study, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sheer, Jens, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Shippingport, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Shippingport. Beaver Valley Hearings. Blackmail of NUS by John Harley, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Shippingport Data, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Shippingport. Infant Mortality, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Shippingport Operator Califorina Inc. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Shippingport Reports I, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Shippingport Reports II, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Shippingport Reports III, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Shoreham Testimony (1970-1971) (See Baby Tooth Files For More) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Smell Mechnaism. Transport of Signals to Brain, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Smoking, Radiation and Health, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Social Control of Science and Technology, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science. Trondheim, 1958-1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Solar Activity. History, Spots, Radiation, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Solon, Leonard, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Solzhenitsyn, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Southard, Virginie, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - South Carolina. Nuclear Fuel Processing. Plant Data, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Nuclear Opposition, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Space Photograph. Earth from Space, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Space Travel. Mars, Life, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Sr90 in Bone. Data - US, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Sr - Effects in Animals and Man, 1960-1971 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Sr90 and Maternal Mortality, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Sr90 and Tooth Decay, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Stachel, John, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Standards, Radiation. USA and Europe, 1961-1978 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Statistical Abstract of US (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Stewart, Alice (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Stokke, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Stroke and CVD, Related to Radiation Statistics, 1971-1979 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Surry Nuclear Reactor Repair Testimony. September 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Survival, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Survival of Man. Outlook '78 Articles, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Symbols and Symbolism. Ancient, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Synergistic Effects Paper. EJS Testimony, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Tarassi (Three Mile Island Litigation), 1980 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Tarasi and Tighe, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Tay-Sachs Disease, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA) and College Retirement Equities Fund (CREF) Reports, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Technion and Medical School, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Technological Assessment, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Technology Lag, US, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Teller, E. History of Hydrogen Bomb, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Tennessee Cancer Distribution, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Teratogenic Effects of Radiation on Mice and Men, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Terns. Congenital Defects, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Test Ban. Total. 1972 Testimony, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Thalidomide Tragedy, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Thermography, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Thermoluminescent Dosimetry (TLD), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Thermonuclear Low-Level Radiation, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Three Mile Island Plant, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Tokuhata, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Tompkins, Edythalena, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Tooth Enamel as Radioactivity Record, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Toxicity, Relevance of Radionucleotides, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Trace Metals and Possible Relation to Radiation, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Travel, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Triga. Bethesda, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Triga Reactors. Accidents, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Triga Reactors. Infant Mortality (My Report), 1971-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Tritium, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Trojan 1990, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Trojan - 1990 Graphs (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Trojan Graphs and Other Materials, 1979-1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Trojan Report, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Trojan Report - 1990, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Trojan Testimony. Plans and Charts, 1963-1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Trondheim - June 1993 Papers, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Trondheim Trip Records, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Tucson Data, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Tucson Tritium Accident, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Turkey Point and Other Tube Failures for Miami, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - TV link Evaluation. Radiology (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists. Greenhouse Effect Reduction, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - United Nations Conference on Environment 1972 - Plans (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Universe Book. Ideas for Appendix, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Uranium, Depleted. Ammunition. Iraq War, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Uranium, Depleted (For Wisconsin), 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Uranium Depletion. Military Use I, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Uranium Depletion. Military Use II, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Uranium Hearings. 1990s (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Uranium Hearings - Salzo '92, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Uranium Mining and Birth Defects 1981 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - USSR Accident, Nuclear and Contamination, 1980-1993 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - USSR, Infant Mortality and Total Mortality, 1981-1996 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - USSR. Moskevich, Victim, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - USSR Reactor Safety and Shut Down, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - USSR. Trip to Kazakstan 1990 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Utah. Infant Mortality, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Vermont Yankee Protest 1990 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Wald, George, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Waltz Mills Accident, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Waste. Export and Disposal. Sludge Toxicity, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Waste Management, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Waste Storage, Nuclear. Kansas, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Water Pollution. Standards and Instruments, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Weik, Mary Hays, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Weinberg, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Weisskopf, V, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Whales Population Decline. Fallout, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Wheeler, John - Opposition to Einstein, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Windscale (Sellaheld) Leukemia (In Children of Workers), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Wisconsin Nuclear Reactor (Lacrosse) Cancer Statistics, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Wisconsin Radiation Study - "Land", 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - World Policy Institute, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - X-Ray Technique Training (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Yankee (Rowe, Mass.) Infant Mortality Data, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Yttrium, Miscelaneous Papers, 1961-1974 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Yttrium - Organ Contamination (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Yucatan Trip - 1983. Ancient Cosmology and Astronomy Knowledge (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Acid Rain (Related to Fallout), 1975 - 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Addiction - Biological Factors and Fallout, 1997 - 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Aging-Related Articles, 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - AIDS 1993 Article (Science) Review, 1987-2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - AIDS and Homosexuality. Biological Origins, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - AIDS in NY State (1991 Article), 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Paper, Material for December 1986, 1985-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Paper (May 1986), 1988 - 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Paper. Slides for Paper on Fallout and AIDS (Immune System), 1986 - 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Air Pollution, 1974 - 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Air Pollution. Deaths, Biological Mechanism, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Air Pollution. Fine Particales and Mortality, 1993-2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Alcalay, Glen, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Alcoholism. Biological and Genetic Factors, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Allerigies. Rise of, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Alpha Particles - After Effects, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Alvarez, Bob - 2003, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) 2000. Our Paper Abstract (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - American Association of Naturopathic Physicians (AANP '95) Key Clipping, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - American Association of Naturopathic Physicians (AANP '95) Lecture and Ideas (Including '94 Lecture), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - American Astronomical Society. Annual Meeting, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - American Astronomical Society. Notices, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - American Physical Society Bulletins, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Amphibian Extinction And Fallout, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Amsterdam, 1985 - 1987 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Ancient Science. Numbers Key, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Ann Arbor Conference. December 1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Anti-Ballistic Missile, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Anti-Nuclear Groups. Nuclear Non-Pollution Treaty Conference, 1995-2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Appolo, PA. Cancer Trial, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Arakawa. Hiroshima and Nagasaki Fallout, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Arkansas. Nuclear Reactors and Infant Mortality Study 1979 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Arp, Halton, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Arthritis Articles, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Asbestos, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Astronomical Society: Bulletins and Announcements, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Astrophysical Journal. Style Manual, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Atomic Veterans California Hearing Testimony May '92, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Atomic Veterans News Letter, 1983-2001 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Atomic Veterans News Letter - 1992, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Atoms and Waste, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Attention Deficit Disorder (ADHD), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Austrian Ambassy Letter on Our Articles, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Author Instruction. Possible Journals, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Authors Instructions. "Science", 1988-2003 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Avery Publications. Review of Secret Fallout, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Babst, Dean ("Suicidal Defenses"), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Ballantine. Burning of My Book Evidence, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Barut, A. O., 1982-1993 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Beaver Valley Hearing Testimony (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - BEIR V. My Analysis For Jay Gould, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - BEIR V Study, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - BEIR VII, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Bell, Steven. SAT and IQ Effects of Nuclear Facilities, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Below Regulatory Concern Status, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Berlin 1992 Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Berlin 1995 - Gould and EJS Slides, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Berlin 1992 #2 Radiation Victims Conference Materials, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Berlin Travel Plans, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Bertell, R, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Bertell, Rosalie. Canadian Reactor, 1987-1999 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Better World Society (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Beyea, Jan, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Birds, Endangered and Fallout (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Black Community. Fallout Effects, 1978-1989 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Black Male Mortality in NY, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Black Minority. Fallout Effects. Infant Mortality. AIDS. Homelessness, 1974-1989 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Boardman, Donnell, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Bogart, Larry - 1988, 1966-1988 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Bogart, Larry's Mailing List, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Bohr, N, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Boice, J.D., 2004 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Book Ideas (1988) Fallout and Health. Chernobyl, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Book Ideas: The Universe, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Book on Immune Deficiency and Fallout (Jay - Feb. 1992) (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Book Plans (1989) Secret Fallout, 1952-1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Book Plans (Secret Fallout Review), 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Book With Jay Gould (1991) Plans, 1986-1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bourmistrov, Viktor (1994 Immigration Case) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Brain Damage and Fallout. Violence, 1988-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Brain Function Research, 1993-1998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Brain and Memory. Biological Basis, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Brain Cancer. County Maps, US, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Breast Cancer Incidence and Mortality in US, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Breast Cancer. NY State Counties Data, 1992-2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Breast Cancer. San Francisco and Philadelphia, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Breast Implants and Connective Tissue Disease, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Breast Milk, Contamination - 1991 Medline, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Bremen. Radnews (Feuerhake). Radiation Risk Factors, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Brodsky, A, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Bronx Medical Waste Incinirator Testimony. 3-19-1992, 1985-1992 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories Lawsuit (1996). Rosen, C.H. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories October 1995 Affidavit (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories - Pollution (Grossman File), 1986-1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories Reply for International Journal of Health Services, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Bross, Irving (Atomic Veterans), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Brown, Jerry (Governor) 1992 Campaign (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Busby, C (1996 London), 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Canadian Atomic Veterans Conference 1995 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Cancer Around Nuclear Plants, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Cancer. Biological Mechanisms. Immune System, etc., 1973-1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Cancer, Breast in Blacks, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Cancer. Cervical 1968-1972 Trend, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Cancer. Childhood. US Incidence. 0-4 Deaths (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Cancer: Colon Fiber. After Closing of Reactors, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Cancer: Gene Identification, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Cancer Incidence Data. Connecticut (From Joe) (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Cancer Incidence and Mortality vs. Nuclear Releases. Graphs for Various Cancer Types. Cancer Mortality Rates vs. Time. (Gould), 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Cancer. International Rise in Cancer. Especially Thyroid, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 34)